<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on 冯某人</title><link>https://alongwy.top/</link><description>Recent content in Home on 冯某人</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alongwy.top/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Language Technology Platform</title><link>https://alongwy.top/projects/creations/language-technology-platform/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 11:35:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alongwy.top/projects/creations/language-technology-platform/</guid><description>Intro An open-source neural language technology platform supporting six fundamental Chinese NLP tasks:
lexical analysis (Chinese word segmentation, part-of-speech tagging, and named entity recognition) syntactic parsing (dependency parsing) semantic parsing (semantic dependency parsing and semantic role labeling). Quickstart 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 from ltp import LTP ltp = LTP() # 默认加载 Small 模型 seg, hidden = ltp.seg([&amp;#34;他叫汤姆去拿外衣。&amp;#34;]) pos = ltp.pos(hidden) ner = ltp.</description></item><item><title>NotFeed: A RSS Reader on GitHub</title><link>https://alongwy.top/projects/creations/notfeed-a-rss-reader-on-github/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 11:40:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alongwy.top/projects/creations/notfeed-a-rss-reader-on-github/</guid><description>NotCraft::NotFeed An RSS reader running entirely from your GitHub repo.
Free hosting on GitHub Pages. No ads. No third party tracking. No need for backend. Content updates via GitHub Actions. Customizable layouts and styles via templating and theming API. Just bring your HTML and CSS. Free and open source. No third-party tracking. How to use it? Github Pages Use the NotFeed-Template generate your own repository.
In the repository root, open Config.</description></item><item><title>Search Results</title><link>https://alongwy.top/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alongwy.top/search/</guid><description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml
1 2 [outputs] home = [&amp;#34;HTML&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;JSON&amp;#34;] Searching additional fileds To search additional fields defined in front matter, you must add it in 2 places.</description></item></channel></rss>